moviegoods.com 2006-12-14

# MovieGoods - Privacy / Security

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for MovieGoods, Inc. ([http://www.MovieGoods.com](http://www.moviegoods.com/))

Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices has also agreed to notify you of:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site;
  2. The organization collecting the information;
  3. How the information is used;
  4. With whom the information may be shared;
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under MovieGoods, Inc.’s control;
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you believe that MovieGoods, Inc. is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please contact our Privacy Advocate by [email](mailto:privacy@moviegoods.com), or telephone at (702) 382-7414, or fax at (702) 388-7414, or by mail at 6000 S. Eastern Avenue, Suite 1B, Las Vegas, Nevada 89104.

**

Information Collection and Use

**

MovieGoods, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. MovieGoods, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.  
Return to Top >>

**

Registration

**

In order to place orders or use any personalized or customized features of this web site, you must first complete our registration form. During registration, you must provide your contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the services on our site for which you have expressed interest.  
Return to Top >>

**

Order

**

We request information from the user on our order form. Obviously, we need your delivery information (name and shipping address), your financial information (credit card number, expiration date, and billing address), and contact information (telephone number, email address).  
Return to Top >>

**

Taxpayer Identification Number (Affiliates Only)

**

Web site owners who register as "affiliates" to earn sales commissions on purchases of other users whom they refer to MovieGoods.com, must provide their taxpayer identification number (your social security number or employer identification number). We cannot make any payments that would cause your affiliate earnings to exceed $600 during a calendar year, until you also submit (to us) an original, signed copy of IRS form W-9. We are required to collect this information from affiliates in order to report your earnings to the U.S. Internal Revenue Service, (and to the taxing authorities of any nation, state, or political subdivision whose laws or regulations we are obligated to respect), and to issue IRS form 1099 to you and the IRS. If you are neither a citizen nor a resident of the United States, you do not need to provide a U.S. taxpayer identification number, but in this case we are required to withhold a portion of your commissions and remit them to the IRS. (You must apply to the IRS for a refund of this money if you do not owe any U.S. income taxes.)

You should not be asked for (and you should never provide) your taxpayer identification number, unless you are applying as an affiliate to earn sales commissions.  
Return to Top >>

**

Mailing Lists and Newsletters

**

During the registration process, during the order process, and at other times at our site, we may ask if you wish to receive email notices regarding our products and services, or regarding related products or services offered by other merchants, or if you wish to subscribe to specific newsletters or discussion lists we may create and manage. You may elect to receive, or not to receive, any of these mailings, and you may change your mind at any time by "logging in" and changing your preferences. Even if you elect to receive these emails, your information will never be disclosed for use by any third party (all such mailings will be done by our staff or agents). If we elect to hire a separate agency or company to manage and deliver our email newsletters or postal mailings, our contract with that agency or company will preclude their using or sharing our customer lists for any other purpose.  
Return to Top >>

**

Cookies

**

A cookie is a piece of data stored by your web browsing software, on your hard disk drive, which is used by a web site to identify and "remember" you during subsequent accesses. MovieGoods, Inc. delivers a "cookie" to you in order to identify and "remember" you during your visit to our site, and during your subsequent visits to our site. If you choose to register, or if you place an order, MovieGoods, Inc. will use the cookie to avoid asking for the same information more than once. For example, we plan to offer a "wish list" feature so that you may store product information in a personal list that will be remembered during later visits to our site. We also want to provide a personal welcome when you return to our site, and we hope that as we learn some of your preferences, we can deliver personalized content and special merchandising offers to you.

We also associate your "cookie" with information about the web site that first referred you to MovieGoods.com, so that we can reward these "affiliates" by paying them a small commission on your purchases, in certain circumstances. Your personal identifying information is never disclosed to our affiliates.

If you reject cookies, you will still have access to our web site, but you may need to enter some information multiple times since we rely on cookies to "remember" that you are the same person who entered information on a prior visit. Some "personalized" or "customized" features of our site may not be available if you reject cookies.  
Return to Top >>

**

Log Files

**

Our web serving software and our e-commerce software each generate "logs" of activity, including specific pages viewed, keywords searched, your IP address, and referral information.

We use this log data, including your IP address, to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. By viewing reports based on log data, we can re-design our web site to be more useful for our customers. We may also use this log data in making merchandising decisions, we may share aggregate information when making merchandising recommendations to our affiliates. Since log files contain only your IP address, they are not linked to any personally identifiable information.  
Return to Top >>

**

Sharing

**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners (including affiliates) and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We maintain our own warehouses and shipping departments, but we may elect at times to ask our third-party suppliers to ship merchandise directly to you on our behalf. We will only disclose to third parties the minimum information required to ship your order, and our contract with any such company will require that they not retain, share, store, or use any personally identifying information for any secondary purposes.

From time to time, MovieGoods may provide the physical mailing addresses of some registered MovieGoods users to partner companies for limited marketing purposes. This information will not include the email addresses and/or phone numbers of any registered users.

We use a credit card verification and processing company to obtain credit card approvals and to bill users for goods and services. The companies we contract with do not retain, share, store, or use any personally identifying information for any secondary purposes. However, your own credit card company may, in some circumstances, make secondary use of your personal information and purchasing history; contact your credit card company for information or to request a copy of your service agreement.

We may partner with other companies to provide specific services, such as coordinating delivery of our opt-in newsletters (see mailing list, above), or to create and deliver "e-greetings". When you sign up for these services, we must share certain information (such as your e-mail address) with our partners in order for you to receive these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. If you discover or suspect any secondary use of your data by any of our partners, please contact our Privacy Officer immediately (see contact information, above).  
Return to Top >>

**

Links

**

This web site contains links to other sites. When you click on such links to external web sites, none of the personal identifying information we gather is shared with those other sites. Please be aware that we (MovieGoods, Inc.) are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
Return to Top >>

**

Surveys & Contests

**

From time-to-time, we may request information from our users, in the form of a survey or contest. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.  
Return to Top >>

**

Security

**

This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL, the best encryption software in the industry. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the "lock" icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked (when you are just "surfing," the icon appears un-locked, or open). 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

If you have any questions about security or privacy at our web site, you can send an email to [privacy@moviegoods.com](mailto:privacy@moviegoods.com).  
Return to Top >>

**

Supplementation of Information

Correction/Updating Personal Information:

**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support.

**

Choice/Opt-In

**

We do not believe in "opt-out" marketing, in which you are automatically sent email unless you take special steps to "opt-out." Instead, we will only send information to our users or customers who have "opted in." Of course, once you "opt in" you can change your mind and "opt out" at any time by logging in to your account and changing your preferences. 

Users who have once opted in, but no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners, may also opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to any email with "unsubscribe" in the subject line.  
Return to Top >>

**

Notification of Changes

**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this web page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  
Return to Top >>
